All Hail the King of Hell
Last Shift is a horror, mystery film directed by Anthony DiBlasi.
Rookie police officer Jessica Loren has been assigned the last shift at a closing police
station and must wait for a hazmat crew to collect biomedical evidence.
Ordered not to leave the station under any circumstances, Jessica comes to learn that it's more than just an
outdated station, it's home to the ultimate embodiment of evil and his devoted bloodthirsty followers.
Jessica is left to fend for herself in the Devil's playground.
Jessica Loren, played by Juliana Harkavy.
John Michael Paymon, played by Joshua Mikel.
Grip Cohen, played by Hank Stone.
Patrick Black, played by J. LaRose.
Kitty Paymon, played by Sarah Sculco.
Dorthea Paymon, played by Kathryn Kilger.
Last Shift is a 2014 American psychological horror film
directed, edited, and co-written by Anthony DiBlasi.
Juliana Harkavy stars as a rookie police officer who is tasked with taking the last shift at a police station
before it is permanently closed, as strange events lead her to believe that it may be haunted.
Joshua Mikel, J.
LaRose, Mary Lankford, Natalie Victoria, and Sarah Sculco also star.
Last Shift premiered at the London FrightFest Film Festival on October 25, 2014, and was
released to video-on-demand on October 6, 2015, to positive reviews from critics.
A remake titled Malum, also directed by DiBlasi, was released in 2023.
The film explores themes of mask, supernatural, hell, telephone, cop.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.